Guide to the Collective: Unconscious Archive 1995-2008 (bulk 1998-2004) MSS 225
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Audio
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - "AntiSlam (1)", March 3, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0212)
    - "AntiSlam (2)", March 17, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0213)
    - "AntiSlam (3)", March 24, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0214)
    - "AntiSlam", March 24, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0215)
    - "AntiSlam (1)", March 24, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0216)
    - "AntiSlam (1)", April 14, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0217)
    - "AntiSlam", April 14, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0218)
    - "AntiSlam (1)", April 21, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0219)
    - "AntiSlam (2)" (side a: "Texas"), April 21, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0220)
    - "AntiSlam", May 5, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0221)
    - "AntiSlam", July 4, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0222)
    - "Faceboy", February 22, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0223)
    - "Faceboy", February 29, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0224)
    - "Faceboy (#2)", February 29, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0225)
      Format: audiocassette
    - "Faceboy (1)", March 7, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0226)
    - "Faceboy (2)", March 7, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0227)
    - "Faceboy (1)", March 21, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0228)
    - "Faceboy (2)", March 21, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0229)
    - "Faceboy (3) (LG - andere kent)", March 21, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0230)
    - "Face[boy] (1)", April 4, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0231)
    - "Faceboy (2)", April 4, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0232)
    - "Face[boy] (1)", April 25, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0233)
    - "Face[boy] (2)", April 25, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0234)
    - "Faceboy" [sibe b: "LG"], May 9, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0235)
    - "For Wolf", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0236)
    - "Fringe Festival, Rev. Billy Show", August 21, 1999 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.)
    - "Kople NYC (#305) [illegible annotations]", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0238)
    - "Match Game", February 28 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0239)
    - "AntiSlam, Rev. Jen (1)", January 6, 1999 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0240)
    - "DM Post 1; NYC Kople (152); side a: Genetica/man [illegible annotations]; side b: Boycot/Israel", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0245)
    - "DM Post 3; NYC Kople", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0246)
    - "Kople NYC (nazi propaganda recordings)", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0255)
    - "Whap spankking; Mee nr NY", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0256)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous
    Access copies for Subseries C may not be available. Please contact a Fales Archivist.
    - "Biet Het Is Prop! (vol. 2)", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0241)
      Original format: CD
    - "Bodibalance Warm-Up For Dancers, Carol Fonda", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0242)
    - "Spoken Words, by Nicolet Brouwn", 1996-2000 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0243)
    - "Alex Chilton, 'Cliches' (Ardent Prod.)", 1994 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0244)
    - "Eat Static, 'Science of the Gods' (Mammoth Records)", 1997 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0247)
    - "F. Labrel", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0248)
    - "Fantasizing in the backseat of a minivan about having kids in a montecarlo", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0249)
      Format: CD
    - "Hanna-Barbera Cartoon Sound FX (Rhino)", 1994 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0250)
    - "Hedwig and the Angry Inch, The Long Grift (Atlantic)", 1999 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0251)
    - "Tom Leher, 'That Was The Year That Was' (Reprise)", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0252)
    - "The M Word", 2002 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0253)
    - "The M Word", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0254)
      Original format: 3" CD
    - "Musigyny 'The CD of the Movie of the Book of the Play'", 2000 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0257)
    - "Narb 'High in the Mountain' (Orchard St. NY)", April 8, 2003 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0258)
    - "The Best of the National Lampoon Radio Hour Vol. 3 (Rhino)", 1996 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0259)
    - "'St. Reverend Jen' and Other Theme Songs by Rob Paravonian", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0260)
    - "Poison Idea/SSD/Bad Brains...", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0261)
    - "Pope John Paul II: The Pope of the Rosary (Radio Vaticana)", 1995 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0262)
    - (illegible scribble), undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0263)
    - "Puccini 'La Boheme' (RCA)", 1964 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0264)
    - "Ramones, It's Alive", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0265)
    - "Rant", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0226)
    - "Sanctity, 'In the Name of the Mother' demo tracks", 2003 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0267)
    - "Smetana Ma Vlast, My Country, Rafael Kubelik (London Records)", 1988 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0268)
    - "Jim Stiene, 'Enema Verite' (Warped Records)", 2003 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0269)
    - "John Todd: Prophecy for the 80s (Kople 133)", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0270)
    - "Mad About Vivaldi", 1985 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0271)
    - "MP3s voor Wolf", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0272)
    - "From Wolf [illegible annotations]", undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0273)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0274)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0275)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0276)
    - untitled, undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0277)
      Original format: microcassette
    - Foreign Language Recordings, undated (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0278)
- Series VII: Computer Discs
  Series VII: Computer Disks contains several 3.5” diskettes and one Zip disk.
  Access copies for computer disks may not be available. Please contact a Fales Archivist.
  - "Bass", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0001)
    Format: 3.5" diskette
  - "Akai Os Backup" [crossed out text: "Manifestations, December 97, #1 of 2 backup"], undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0002)
  - "Spart 2, disk 3 of 3", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0003)
  - "Spart 2, disk 2 of 3; Mikon 2", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0004)
  - "Spart 2, disk 1 of 3; Mikon 1", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0005)
  - "Manifestations January '98, disk 3 of 3", 1998 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0006)
  - "Manifestations, January '98, disk 2 of 3", 1998 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0007)
  - "Manifestations, December '97, #2 of 2", 1997 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0008)
  - "Manifestations, December '97, #1 of 2", 1997 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0009)
  - "Manifestations, December '97, #2 of 2", 1997 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0010)
  - "Manifestations, January 98, disk 1 of 3", 1998 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0011)
  - "Hanna Barbera #1", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0012)
  - "Hanna Barbera #2", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0013)
  - "Hanna Barbera #3", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0014)
  - "Hanna Barbera #4", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0015)
  - "Hanna Barbera #5", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0016)
    ID: 225.3.0016
  - "Hanna Barbera #6", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0017)
  - "Hanna Barbera #7", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0018)
  - "Man EP 5, disk 1, bomber and machine gun (L)", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0019)
  - "Man EP 5, Disk 5 (No 4), explosion", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0020)
  - "Manifestations, Fifth Column #1", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0021)
  - "Manifestations, 5th Column #2", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0022)
  - "Manifestations, 5th Column #3", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0023)
  - "Penis Plunge, Stab, Doorbell, Door", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0024)
  - "Bad Things", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0025)
  - "Akai 5900, K-muse, LA - Sustained Sounds", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0026)
  - "Akai 5900, glass ball, choir, voice-string", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0027)
  - "Synth bass", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0028)
  - "Man EP 5, disk 7, gas hiss, stake plunge, punch 1, punch 2, braincry", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0029)
  - "Man EP 5, disk 9, bootmarch, air raid", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0030)
  - "Man EP 5, disk 10, gun, punch, sword", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0031)
  - "Falling Women and Rocks", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0032)
  - [untitled], undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0033)
  - [untitled], undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0034)
  - [untitled], undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0035)
  - [untitled], undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0036)
  - "Win 98 startup; blank", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0037)
  - "Playpractice pictures, 7/99", 1999 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0038)
  - "Resumes", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0039)
  - "Collective Backup", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0040)
    Format: Zip disk
- Oversize
  Oversize includes oversized material from: Series I, Subseries A, B; Series III; and Series IV.
  - Oversize Series I: Subseries A
    - Monthly Calendar, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 279 Church St. blueprint, undated (Map-case 1.B, Folder 1)
  - Oversize Series I: Subseries B
    - Alliance of Resident Theatres [post-9/11?] poster, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Misc. production posters, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Signed posters - "The Sayanas"; "The Caedmon Kids", undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Annie Sprinkle posters, ISWFACE (International Sex Worker Foundation for Art, Culture and Education), 2002 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - "Deadly Departures", Christine Negroni book poster, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Videotaped performance notice, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - The Porno Jim Show poster, undated (Map-case 1.B, Folder 2)
    - N-Ho-Tep production posters, undated (Map-case 1.B, Folder 3)
    - Fabric C:U sign [used in Monster Parade, Mermaid Parade], undated (Map-case 1.B)
  - Oversize Series III
    - Misc. photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Oversize Series IV
    - Misc. photocopies - patterns/artwork, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)